drizzydrake.org 2016-10-16

# Privacy Policy - DRIZZY DRAKE

This website is operated by or for Orelus Investments, LLC (“ **DRIZZYDRAKE.ORG** “). The following rules set forth **DRIZZYDRAKE.ORG** ‘s rights to collect and make use of certain information.

Collection and Use of Information: In addition to any personally identifying information you may voluntarily provide during your visit to this website, **DRIZZYDRAKE.ORG** may recognize and record certain other information, including without limitation, your computer’s unique IP address, and/or any other information concerning your use of this website. **DRIZZYDRAKE.ORG** reserves the right to use any information it collects at this website for any legal purpose, including without limitation by sending you information concerning future products, activities and/or promotions, and/or by sharing your information with third-parties in connection with certain promotions, products, programs and/or services. You may contact us by mail at Orelus Investments, LLC, 14970 Durham Lane, Davie, FL 33331 to request that **DRIZZYDRAKE.ORG** remove your information from its promotional lists.

Secure Transactions: In processing any sale transaction made on this website, **DRIZZYDRAKE.ORG** uses Secure Sockets Layer software (“SSL”), which is industry standard to secure online transactions. SSL is designed to encrypt your personal information, including your name, address and credit card data, and is designed to prevent others from accessing such information as it travels over the Internet. Notwithstanding **DRIZZYDRAKE.ORG** ‘s efforts, no transmission of data over the Internet is guaranteed to be completely secure and such transmission is at your own risk.

Cookies: Cookies are small text files that contain a string of alphanumeric characters. **DRIZZYDRAKE.ORG** reserves the right to use “cookies” at this website, by which one computer transaction may be related with a later one. By way of example, cookies may be used to save passwords or preferences or otherwise keep track of website access. For more information about cookies please visit: [www.allaboutcookies.org/cookies/](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/cookies/)

Third Party Cookies:  
**DRIZZYDRAKE.ORG** also uses third party third party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit this website. These companies may use information about your visits to this website (not including your name, address, or other personal information) to provide advertisements on this website, other sites and other forms of [media](http://www.drizzydrake.org/category/media/ "media") about goods and services that may be of interest to you. In providing advertisements, a unique third party cookie may be placed on your browser. **DRIZZYDRAKE.ORG** does not control or have access to these cookies. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/consumer/opt_out.asp)

Children: Notwithstanding the foregoing, **DRIZZYDRAKE.ORG** does not seek to collect any personally identifiable information of children under 13 years of age and no such information should be submitted and/or posted to this website. 

Media: **DRIZZYDRAKE.ORG** does not take ownership of ANY of the [photos](http://www.drizzydrake.org/category/photos/ "photos") or media found on the website, they are copyrighted to they’re respectful owners. Media files such as mixtapes and [music](http://www.drizzydrake.org/category/music/ "music") downloads are not hosted on our site nor do we claim ownership. If you are the “Owner” of photos and would like us to remove them or correctly credit them, [click here](http://www.drizzydrake.org/image-copyrights/). Photos are published on the website under the [Fair Use Act](http://www.copyright.gov/fls/fl102.html), and no copyright infringement is intended. Once emailed by any OWNER, we will take it upon our selves to remove the specific image or file from our website.

**Fair Use** is a limitation and exception to the exclusive right granted by copyright law to the author of a creative work. In United States copyright law, fair use is a doctrine that permits limited use of copyrighted material without acquiring permission from the rights holders. Examples of fair use include commentary, criticism, **news reporting** , research, teaching, library archiving and scholarship. It provides for the legal, unlicensed citation or incorporation of copyrighted material in another author’s work under a four-factor balancing test.

California Privacy Rights: Under California Civil Code sections 1798.83-1798.84, California residents are entitled to ask **DRIZZYDRAKE.ORG** for a notice identifying the categories of personal customer information which **DRIZZYDRAKE.ORG** shares with its affiliates and/or third parties for marketing purposes, and providing contact information for such affiliates and/or third parties. If you are a California resident and would like a copy of this notice, please submit a written request to the following address: Orelus Investments, LLC, 14970 Durham Lane, Davie, FL 33331, Attn: General Counsel. In your request, please specify that you want a “ **DRIZZYDRAKE.ORG** ‘s California Privacy Rights Notice,” and allow thirty (30) days for a response.

LIMITATION ON LIABILITY: UNDER NO CIRCUMSTANCE SHALL **DRIZZYDRAKE.ORG** , ANY OF ITS AFFILIATES (INCLUDING BY WAY OF COMMON OWNERSHIP), AND/OR ANY OF THEIR OWNERS, OFFICERS, EMPLOYEES OR AGENTS, BE LIABLE TO YOU FOR ANY INDIRECT, SPECIAL, PUNITIVE, INCIDENTAL, EXEMPLARY OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, WHETHER IN AN ACTION UNDER CONTRACT, NEGLIGENCE AND/OR ANY OTHER LEGAL THEORY, ARISING IN ANY WAY FROM OR IN CONNECTION WITH YOUR ACCESS, USE OR INABILITY TO ACCESS OR USE THIS WEBSITE.

Applicable Law: The laws of the State of Florida shall govern all matters relating to this website privacy policy, without giving effect to any principles of conflict of law. By your use of this website, you irrevocably submit to the exclusive jurisdiction of the state and federal courts located in Broward County, Florida with respect to resolution of disputes arising hereunder. 

Policy Changes: **DRIZZYDRAKE.ORG** reserves the right to change this policy, in whole or part, at any time in its sole and absolute discretion, without prior notice, effective upon providing the updated policy on this website. If you have any [questions](http://www.drizzydrake.org/category/questions/ "questions") concerning this policy, please submit your written questions to Orelus Investments, LLC, 14970 Durham Lane, Davie, FL 33331, Attn: General Counsel.
